Finding Aid for the William James Campbell Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
William James Campbell Papers
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0069
.84 linear_feet
- Outgoing Correspondence
  - February 1937- March 1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - October 1938- December 1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - January 1939- May 1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - September 1939- December 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - January 1940- May 1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - October 1940- December 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - January 1941- March 1941 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - April 1941- May 1941 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - September 1941- October 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - November 1941- December 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - January 1942-June 1942 and September 1944 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Incoming Correspondence
  - Adair, Frank E.- A (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bagby, Charles Lee- Bagby, J. Tom (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bahr, Eleanor- Brown, J. Monroe (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cady, Burt- Cook, G. W., Jr. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Day, Rufus- Donnell, Edith (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Edwards, George- Evans, James (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Eversull, Harry Kelso (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Findlay, J. F. – Green, Shirley E. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Hadden, William J., Jr. Hutchins, William J. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Jackson, D. Orville Jones, Thomas J. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Keck, Samuel W Key, Carl (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - King, Elisha A. Kurn, J. M. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Laub, D. Kenneth Leiper, Henry Smith (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Lidstone, Winsloe J. Longworth, W. H. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Mac Quarrie, G. R. Myers, Virgil E. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Nadel, Thomas W. Ottaway, William W. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Parsons, Edward Quimby, A. K. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Rahill, John Wells Rucks, A. R. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Schulz, F. A. Irwin Slater, Arnold (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Smith, Charles W. – Smith, Helen Frances (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Sp?- Swain, Ramsey (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Swann, Arthur- Swann, Walter (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Swartz, Arthur G. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Sweet, Milo (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Tolman, Mayo- Tuttle, Warren W. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Usher, Guy S. – Vincent, George (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Weigle, L. A. – Wingfield, Marshall (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous Materials
  - Unidentified Correspondence, Clippings, Pamphlets, Invitations (Box 2, Folder 39)